DETAILS

hello@arkadiuszbachorski.com
github.com/arkadiuszbachorski
arkadiuszbachorski.com

SKILLS

- TypeScript, JavaScript
- React, Next.js, Vue
- Redux, functional programming
- Cypress, Jest, Vitest
- REST API, GraphQL
- react-query, RTK query
- HTML5, accessibility
- CSS3, Tailwind, SCSS, styled-components
- PHP, Laravel, MySQL
- Python, Django
- Git, GitHub, Figma, Linear, Jira
- Attentive to details and clean code

LANGUAGES

Polish - native speaker

English - **B2**

HOBBIES

New technologies, traveling, cars, motorcycles, gym, squash

Arkadiusz Bachorski

Fullstack Web Engineer

Ambitious programmer with 5+ years of experience in building complex web products. On a mission to deliver exceptional experiences for both users and developers. Excited about new challenges and meeting new people. Known for hard work and proactive attitude. Flexible, learns new things and adjusts to the team flow rapidly. Team player and one-man-army at once.

EXPERIENCE

Zypsy - Senior Fullstack Engineer

September 2021 - now

- selected work <u>Formless</u>, <u>Smoothie</u>, <u>captionary.ai</u>
- building engineering team and improving processes
- providing technical expertise

Robust Intelligence - Senior Frontend Engineer

September 2021 - now

- building frontend of <u>RI platform</u> app to protect and validate AI models. Data, visualizations and variations heavy.
- building design system components library
- improved both UX and DX greatly by reworking data fetching architecture

Apptention - Senior Frontend Engineer

August 2020 - October 2021

- built <u>mTab Marketplace</u> data analysis and visualization marketplace platform
- contributed to <u>SaaS Boilerplate</u> opinionated SaaS stack, packed with features
- implemented REST and GraphQL APIs in Django
- became the youngest senior in the company

IT Computer Partner - Fullstack Engineer

April 2018 - November 2019

- built React apps integrated with own Laravel REST APIs, Facebook APIs and Google Maps API
- created server-side apps based on Laravel and MySQL
- built backend microservcies

EDUCATION

IT Technician

Secondary School Complex No. 1 in Jarocin

2016 - 2020

Specialization: web applications and databases